Alex Buhai

368-299-7666 | oleksandr.buugay@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/alex-buhai-95a35227b https://github.com/OleksandrBuhai

SUMMARY

Experienced front end developer with a professional background in crafting complex, interactive web projects since 2021. High at cross-browser development, web standards, usability, responsive web development, and application architecture. I enjoy creating products that will benefit people in the future.

EDUCATION

IT-Incubator.io

Front-End Developer May 2020 - May 2021

NTUU KPI

Studied Manufacturing Engineering Aug. 2015 - May 2019

Kviv. Ukraine

Konotop, Ukraine

IPTKisSUMDU

College Degree in Manufacturing Technology May 2013 - May 2015

Experience

Front-End Developer Apr 2023 - Jul 2023

Berlin Labs LLC Remote

• Developing new user-facing features using React

• Participation in the development of a project for the sale of photo \ video.

• Optimizing components for maximum performance

• Building reusable components

Front-End Developer

Jun 2022 - Mar 2023 Mladá Boleslav, CZ

Self employ

• Development of landing pages;

• Developing features to enhance the user experience

- Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.
- Ensuring web design is optimized for smartphones
- Fix Bugs

Production Supervisor

May 2019 - Dec 2021 Škoda Auto Mladá Boleslav, CZ

• Addressing technical challenges

• Managed both equipment and a team, ensuring smooth operations and quality standards

• Addressing technical challenges

Dec 2016 - Jul 2017 Graphic Assistant Kyiv, Ukraine

Mindy Support

• Data Processing for Neural Networks

• Image Processing for Future Use

Projects

Portfolio | React, JavaScript, CSS

• https://oleksandrbuhai.github.io/Portfolio/

• Working with libraries framer-motion , React styled component, tsparticles

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Lanuages: English, Czech, Ukranian

ProgLanguages: JavaScript, TypeScript HTML/CSS

Frameworks: React, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Tailwind CSS, jQuery, Material-UI

Developer Tools: Git, Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ